What's up, losers?
Get in.
We're playing Isaac.
Cheers.
Oh, no!
I just spilled everywhere.
Who shook my can?
My can is shook.
Shook once, part two.
Let's try that again.
Fuck.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
Sims has not ended, don't worry.
We're playing more Sims soon.
I was just not feeling it too much lately.
I was pretty obsessed with XCOM.
I still am.
XCOM kinda stole the limelight from Sims a little bit, I gotta be honest.
But we're playing more Sims.
I'm still excited about it.
And guys, I know I said I was gonna do challenges today and greed runs.
I'm gonna have to retract that statement.
I retract that statement about your cunt-fucking-kids.
Sorry.
That's an in-bruge reference.
I didn't actually mean anything about anyone's kids.
I'm kidding.
I will not be doing greed or challenge.
Because I just don't feel like it right now.
I wanna... I'm having more fun with the main game.
And I wanna get my... I wanna get my... my streak going.
Because I'm at a streak of one right now.
And who knows?
Hey, hey.
If we get a win immediately and we get a streak of two...
Then I'm doing greed or challenge.
Yes.
Because...
A streak of two is very rare for me.
And just having the number there would be great.
You know?
Coke tier list.
Uh... Coke zero at the top.
Everything else below.
Pretty much.
Then again.
This is all for the sugar-free ones.
Obviously the ones with sugar taste better.
Jackie's meowing in the background.
Even though I just played with her.
Isn't that right?
She wants more playtime.
You can't get enough of the playtime.
That... that... that...
Okay, you got me!
That was me meowing!
I did it!
It was... I don't even have a cat.
It's all fake, guys.
AI generated on the second channel.
What song is this?
Uh... I don't know.
Something from YouTube.
From the YouTube library, I guess.
I don't actually have a name for it right now.
It's just in my foobar with, uh...
No name.
Yeah, Jackie's AI.
I'm also AI.
Guys, your whole life is AI.
Ever since you were born, you thought it was real.
Nothing is real.
Everything is fake.
Will you take pills today?
When will you take pills?
I... I...
Yes, I will, of course, take pills.
I love taking pills.
In Isaac.
I was born from your one-year-old playing Minecraft blind.
Okay?
I will play Subnautica 2, but, uh...
When it's done.
Hey, I'm not gonna taste the meal when it's, like, raw.
You know?
Let them add the spices.
Let them get the pasta al dente first before I start eating it.
Where will you wear weeks?
Exactly.
I habitually watch that video, you know?
Like, it's a video that always comes back around.
And it's like the YouTube algorithm knows exactly when I need it.
Then it gives it to me.
It's feeding me, you know, with a spoon.
And I go, ah...
Putting it in my mouth and I go, mmm...
That's good content.
Yes, I'm bald.
Always been.
I can't produce hair on my body, actually.
I'm also blind.
Yes.
I've never been able to see.
So you should be impressed at what I'm able to do, okay?
I'm bald.
I'm blind.
Yep.
Thoughts on gummy bears?
I loved them as a kid.
Not so much anymore.
I don't know what changed.
Thank you for contributing your hair to the orphans.
That's horrible.
I just imagine kids all over the world wearing tiny bits of my hair.
That has been glued on their heads.
That's terrible.
Ew.
How are you reading our chats if you're blind?
Because I have the neural link.
It's next level, guys.
Yeah.
I know what I'm going to say and what you guys are going to say before you say them.
Because I analytically analyze the algorithm and, you know, based on your search records and everything else, I produce, I synthesize, whatever you're about to say next.
That's a Curry Barker reference.
Gummy worms or bears?
Anything that's sour, I love it.
If it's sour, I eat it.
Yes.
I can definitely feel games.
That's one of the reasons I play them.
It's one of the few things in life that make me feel something.
Man, I don't know if you can hear that.
Jackie is sprinting all over the apartment right now.
She has Sumis.
Jumping up and down furniture.
Uh, Undertale Sans.
Just watch the VOD on YouTube.
I also earn more money that way, actually.
Livestreams actually don't make much money.
You know?
Because this is my living now.
The VODs, the VOD people are actually the real bread givers.
Which is kind of crazy to think about.
Twitch doesn't, uh...
Doesn't actually pay very much.
It's crazy.
You mean the AI can't assume...
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Of course.
I mean, this whole thing is scripted also.
Everything I say is scripted.
Alright, I'll watch twice.
Okay, guys.
I'm gonna play some Isaac.
And we're not gonna...
I know I say this every time, but...
Today, I actually feel really good.
And I think I'm gonna be playing flawlessly.
I just had some great runs in XCOM.
I don't know.
I feel like I've gotten professional at that game.
I'm fucking owning it.
And I'm gonna take that energy...
And I'm gonna put it into...
Isaac.
Oh, yeah.
I'm gonna channel that energy.
Yeah!
Look at that house on that hill.
Let's pick an OP character.
Okay, what have I not done on this?
So, we've done Heart.
We've done Isaac.
We've done Satan, I think.
We've also done the speedrun thingy.
Star, I don't remember what is.
I don't know.
Let me see here.
Honestly?
I kinda wanna do Cain again.
I did Cain last time, and it went really well.
Oh, oh, the last one in the bottom right is going home.
The thing is, though, on Cain and Isaac, I tried going home, but I didn't find a key.
I was just unlucky.
But I was gonna try and unlock their counterparts, you know?
These guys.
Couldn't do it, unfortunately.
Jacob and Esau has no completion marks on them right now.
That could be a thing that I could try and go for.
It is kind of difficult to play.
If I just go for the heart.
We can go for the heart.
Just keep it really simple.
No bullshit.
We can do it.
I believe.
Um.
I have to remember how I...
Uh, what did it say?
Bolt control.
Oh, right.
Yeah.
Okay.
We're gonna go...
Mega slow.
Super slow.
We're gonna play tactically.
It's gonna be amazing.
Um.
Okay, this is annoying, actually.
Maybe do like this.
I'm gonna destroy this wall over here.
That should do it.
Okay.
No secret there, unfortunately.
But it was a good effort.
Is that what I think it is?
Oh, I thought it was Ipecac.
Increases the damage of tears fired from Isaac's left eye.
Okay.
Right.
That's probably...
Oh, oh.
Tinted rock in here.
Let's not forget.
Uh, Isao is the red guy.
I think I can afford to go in here.
Oh, he got...
Wow.
Uh.
Flies?
Okay.
You go first.
There we go.
Solid.
Dude, why the fuck did I pick Jacob and Isao?
I just realized, like...
I was supposed to be playing safe and OP characters.
And to get the streak up and not lose a single time.
And then I picked this.
Arguably the worst.
It's not gonna work out.
I'm just gonna mentally prepare myself for that.
We got a pill up here.
Two pills.
We got a bomb.
Let's do the, uh...
Tinted rock.
Oh, we're making two bombs at a time, right?
So check this out.
This is some next level shit, guys.
Hey!
Not bad.
Come here.
Uh, what is that?
The small rock.
Damage, tears, less speed.
Okay.
But the speed is gonna affect both of us, right?
Who has the least amount of damage?
It's actually Jacob.
Jacob.
Yeah.
Good.
That's not bad.
I like it.
Good start.
Do you want to get the pills, though?
Another pill.
Oh, god.
Okay.
So far, so good.
Come here.
That's not that bad.
I feel like I've gotten lucky with these rooms.
Nothing too difficult or crazy so far.
Good start.
Okay.
We still have a shop.
But I don't have any money.
But it's worth going inside anyway.
Just in case there's free money to be had.
Oh, wait.
Nah.
I can't get anything.
Couldn't even blow up the donation machine to get money if I wanted.
Priority is to get health for Ezow.
That's the priority.
Oh, there's four of them.
There's three of them.
Dude, that was easy.
What the hell?
That's nice.
That's for Ezow.
Yes, dude.
This is great.
Good start.
And we're keeping it simple.
We gotta...
We're taking the easiest route we can.
Which means...
What does that mean?
I guess we're going to Isaac.
That's like the easiest, right?
There's nothing easier.
Yeah.
Good.
Okay.
I think we have to go for angels.
Simply because keeping track of two health bars is hard enough in itself.
So, you know, reducing my HP on any one of these characters is a huge risk.
Good.
Very nice.
Uh, yeah.
Kind of want to bomb these skulls.
Uh, yeah, okay.
Four coins.
Nope.
Bad idea.
I'm looking for tinted rocks.
There are none.
Get him.
Very good.
I'm proud of myself so far.
This is very...
Uh, organized and...
Calm gameplay.
You know, no overreactions on anything so far.
Calm and calculated.
Okay, Ezow, you get this one.
Even here I'm playing it safe.
Max range.
Very nice.
Still no, uh, treasure room, though.
Come on, then.
I think this character actually has the potential to be one of the best characters.
Simply because of the fact that you have two characters shooting more bullets.
You know, the potential is there.
It's just very difficult.
Maybe in an ideal world.
Oh, my God.
See, that was a little scary, you know?
And you get separated like that.
That was sick.
Stay together.
Even here, I go like this.
Any of those speed zones, like the cobwebs, are gonna mess it up for me, right?
They're gonna desynchronize my guys.
So it's important to try and avoid those.
Six coins.
It's not great.
Rubber cement.
Ooh, uh...
Let's put that on Jacob.
His tears are better.
So having them bounce around is better.
Mom's coin purse.
Not super exciting stuff in here.
I mean, I could buy the little bundle there.
Wait!
Oh, my God!
Planetarium!
Jupiter!
Less speed.
Ooh.
Plus two health.
When standing still, Isaac rapidly gains a speed increase.
Moving expensed this bonus while spawning fart clouds that poison enemies.
Makes Isaac immune to poison gas spawned by enemies.
Uh, okay.
Well, this is what I'm worried about.
If I take this on Jacob or Esau, is it only gonna speed up one of them?
Because if that's the case, this is kinda risky shit.
I'm not sure I like this.
We have to experiment, though.
I don't know.
No!
It's only one of them!
Oh, wait.
Are we moving together at max speed?
Wait, hold on.
Let me try and stand still.
Gaining speed.
Hey!
That's good, then!
Nice!
Okay!
I'm glad I tested.
Very nice.
I actually really like this item.
Ah, the problem is he's now a bigger character.
That's one thing.
He's fast.
Which makes it harder to stay close to each other.
You know?
That's one big disadvantage.
Yeah, let's get out of here.
No bombs to look for secrets or anything like that.
Let's get ready.
Oh, not this guy!
I'm gonna stand still.
There we go.
Get poisoned, nerd.
Dude, not bad at all.
Not bad at all.
Growth hormones.
More damage.
I should give that to Isao.
He needs damage.
Yeah.
Okay, good.
We're not taking demon.
Yeah.
No demon.
We're going angel.
Okay.
Oi, oi, oi.
Get poisoned.
Dude, that was solid.
Good.
Stay together.
Oh, no.
I'm gonna poop on this guy.
Yeah, you like that?
You like that?
You son of a gun.
A pill.
Uh.
No.
But wait, it's only one of us who has amnesia.
The other guy has perfectly fine memory.
Come on.
We have two brains.
Let's use them.
Two minds are better than one, right?
Apparently not.
Okay.
Yeah, I have no batteries you can steal.
Uh, Ghost Pepper.
Chance to fire a spectral flame.
It deals heavy damage and block enemy shots.
I like that.
Let's give it to...
Uh, Isaac.
No, Jacob.
His name is not Isaac.
Okay, align them.
Actually, the fat guy is the one with the most HP.
You're the vanguard here.
You need to be in front.
Oh!
Yeah, step into my office down here.
It's nice and warm.
Okay.
Man, I hate being lost.
Oh, I have no keys.
Shit.
Yeah, I get burned.
Okay, let's give it to...
Jacob.
Shit.
Man, the pills have not been on my side today.
I love the farts!
They're incredible.
Stay in open space.
Good.
Nice.
A key.
That's good.
We can get to the shop now.
Ten coins, though.
Maybe I wait a bit.
No, let's go have a look.
I need to plan everything around the shop, you know?
Depending on what's in there...
I could decide to do other things.
Okay, a blue heart is pretty good.
Oh, BFF!
Doubles the damage of familiars.
I don't think Jacob or Ezau counts as a familiar, unfortunately.
But it is worth trying, right?
So I think we should try and save up for it.
Otherwise, we're gonna get the blue heart.
Like, he's technically my character.
Like, he shouldn't count as a familiar, but who knows?
This game is a bit quirky.
With things like that, so it could, you know?
Oh, you bastard!
Pill?
Come on, please.
The third pill.
Be good.
Nice!
Good shit.
Uh, so we have the boss here.
Yeah, let's go for it.
The stain.
Get farted on.
Oh, that's gonna be tough to dodge on this character.
Oh, God!
Shit.
Stand still to fart.
There we go.
Very good, very good.
Unfortunately, we got hit, so we lost the angel.
Well, the possibility of an angel.
Yeah.
Give me that.
I'm gonna go heal up.
The hermit.
Um...
I think I should go buy the blue heart.
For Jacob.
Or, hold on.
Let's go back to the beginning here, because I may have missed something.
I am blind, right?
I mean, I have curse of the blind or whatever it's called.
So I don't actually know where I've been.
Wait, this looks...
I think I've...
Have I gone here?
I have.
Oh, I have not gone here.
What the hell is that sound?
Something just exploded.
Oh, look at that thing up there!
That's a good mushroom, guys!
Boy, am I glad I went back.
That is huge.
Just like Esau.
Du feta sau.
Pulseworm.
Um, I mean, yeah.
I don't have any, so...
Me as well.
Speed and range.
Wait, who has the least range?
Jacob.
Oh, but hold on.
We can make Esau smaller.
Let's make him smaller.
Size down, right?
Hey!
Now we're about the same size again.
I like it.
The range is a little bit disproportionate now, but it is what it is.
I think it's worth it.
Okay, so we can bomb here.
And we can bomb here if I'm smart about it.
Can I actually?
That's crazy.
But how am I gonna...
Sick!
Not bad, eh?
Why can't I see what that is?
Oh, I need to be there with Jacob.
Okay.
Spawns a beggar.
No keys left, unfortunately.
Gives Isaac a curse of the lost.
Bro.
Again.
Fight club?
I could do with a bit of fight club.
Why not?
Sup, son.
Yeah, you like farts?
That's for you.
No rewards, huh?
That's weird.
Oh, god.
Oh, man.
Okay.
No door here.
Oh, we have a key now.
Ah.
Oh, well.
We got a key back.
I'm happy.
Could go in here.
I mean, now that we already beat the boss, and we have healing, let's do it.
Yeah.
Not bad.
Let's go heal up.
And I think that's it.
Wait, there's actually a door here.
Aha.
Justice.
Ooh.
I like that.
And now we should be done here.
So we actually have two bombs.
Could look for a secret.
But it's too risky when I have curse of the lost, because I don't really know where the hell I am.
Yeah.
Let's go.
Oh, wait.
I should have bought the fucking blue heart.
Oh, why do I always realize it right when I jump down the hole?
Damn it.
Okay, shit.
Six, seven percent angel.
Scary.
Get poisoned by my farts!
Step into my hotbox.
Arcade.
Hmm.
Dude, I could have bought the BFF.
I had so many coins as well.
Oh my god, what a misplay.
Shit.
Oh no.
Man, the farts are so good.
Especially for situations like this.
Oh my god.
Actually, uh...
Jacob, stay behind, fat guy.
Dude, I'm kind of killing it.
Am I not?
Yes!
There we go.
Buffer achieved.
Actually, Jacob should be in front now.
Because he's the one with the bigger buffer.
Yeah, this farting system that we have going on here is...
Fantastic.
For Jacob and Esau.
What an item.
Uh, wait.
Yeah.
Ho-ho-ho-ho-ho-ho!
So nice.
Okay, so check it out.
This is what we're gonna do.
Here.
And here.
So we're gonna bomb and go down and left.
Okay.
I was gonna check for, uh, you know...
Secret room.
Uh, spectral tears in a rabid looping pattern?
I don't like that at all.
We gotta keep things consistent here.
Good.
I'm not panicking.
I'm playing calm and collected here.
This is great.
No!
Not that room.
Go fast.
Run!
Ho-ho-ho-ho!
Oh!
The D6!
Uh, bops.
Dude, that is amazing.
Let me bomb here.
And here.
Uh, wait.
I gave it to...
Jacob.
Boy, am I glad I picked it up before I picked up the other one!
I thought I could pick up both!
Holy shit!
Imagine I picked up the other one and the D6 disappeared.
I almost did it!
Wow.
Holy crap!
Okay, let's go like this now.
Oh yeah.
I got your number now.
Sick.
Lovely.
Okay, we got a shop!
That's great!
Oh yeah, this looks good.
So we have a pill.
We have a...
I forgot what this one was.
Fanny pack.
Hmm.
Nah.
Oh, this card is the one that...
Oh, I don't actually remember.
It spawns...
Two cards or something?
I think.
Fat guy needs one of these.
You're gonna take, uh, this one?
A chaos card!
Okay, so what is that?
Oh man, I don't remember what that does.
Wait, what?
What the hell did I do?
I threw the card into the wall.
Alright.
Weird.
Well, I'm gonna save my, uh, re-roll for the angel room, obviously.
Yeah, I'll be back.
Maybe.
Come at me.
The flames you shoot is so good.
I have a bomb.
I could get in there.
In fact, I can also check for a secret.
So I go here, I go down and left.
Wait, what?
Oops.
Nope.
Don't do that.
Oh my god!
I'm a gamer!
Actually insane.
Uh...
Yeah, give that to...
Jacob.
I like it.
Uh, come on.
Okay, I don't like this very much.
Okay, here we go, here we go!
Six, seven angel!
I believe!
Do you believe?
It's Peep.
He's actually kinda tough.
His son of a gun.
Oh god, we got hit.
Fuck.
No, no, no, no.
Yeah, we made it!
Six, seven!
Yes!
Okay, uh...
Who needs range?
It is Jacob.
Now we have equal range.
I love it.
Already, I'm underwhelmed by this.
Yeah, I hate this.
We're gonna reroll.
Nice!
That's good.
I mean, it's not fantastic, but it's good.
Uh, who needs more damage?
Probably Jacob.
Uh, Jacob, yeah.
That's good.
We can also bomb some of this.
Uh, running around this room is going to be a little bit scary.
Because there's so many flames.
Fighting this angel is gonna be...
you know...
a little risky.
So if I bomb here, I quickly go...
right, and then...
I...
I meet up, and...
Suck on that!
I'm actually surprised at my own ability to do this.
This is some next-level stuff happening here.
Oh, shit.
Never mind.
I'll take it back.
This is very medium level.
Uh, key piece, sure.
Very good.
Uh, I think we're done here.
Could look for a secret, maybe.
Oh, I think I know where there's a secret.
I see it already.
Right down here.
But let's check all the rooms.
No.
Oh, I don't like that.
I'm gonna take a chance here.
Shit.
Okay, that was a bad chance.
I fucked it up.
Uh, okay.
So it's 17 coins.
Is there anything we need from the shop before we leave?
I guess I could get the fanny pack.
Not the worst idea.
Who's more likely to take damage?
Probably Jacob.
He's a little bit bigger right now.
I can't wait to see my actual HP.
I hate not being able to see my HP.
Can I please not have a curse?
All right.
The dank depths.
Dude, we're doing great on HP.
Would you look at that?
This has to be the greatest start to a Jacob and Esau run I've ever done.
Not that I've done a lot, but, you know.
Still.
What hit me?
Oh, wait.
You're the one.
Oh, God.
There we go.
Oh, shit.
Teleport to the shop.
Ah, I actually kind of like that.
No, I have two coins.
It's not that great.
Oh, what?
He was close to me.
I'm taking a lot of damage.
We gotta slow things down a little bit.
Jacob needs to be in front now, at all times.
Ooh, that's nice.
Give it to the fat guy.
Kidney bean.
Oh, I actually really like this one.
I could re-roll it, but I'm not going to.
It's actually just that good.
The only problem is, if I have to use an item, I think I have to click control, and then space.
No, wait.
How does that work?
Wait.
Let me try something.
Pick this up.
So that does that.
And if I now...
If I now give it to...
him...
Wait.
What?
I don't want to accidentally use my D6 here.
This is the problem.
Fuck.
I don't know how to use it.
So if I hold control, then they both sort of fade out.
Guys, how the fuck do I use the bottom right item?
Tell me.
Rotund.
I need to know.
I'm alt-tabbing.
Q?
Okay.
Alright.
Got it.
Okay.
That's surely not going to bite me in the ass with muscle memory and space being the active item.
I can tell you already, I'm going to accidentally use the D6.
This is not...
I mean, I need to have the D6 on Esau and not Jacob.
I need to switch them around.
Actually, I can do that, right?
No, I can't.
Fuck.
Oh no.
Who had what?
Give me that one.
And you take these two.
More cards.
The farting noise is going to get old.
Pretty fast.
I mean, being able to hold two cards is actually pretty sick.
I may come back and buy that.
Also, it is a fat guy that has the charm.
Okay.
He's so charming.
Kill each other.
Lovely.
More range?
Jacob.
And then we had this thing.
Judgment.
What hearts, huh?
The flame you fire is actually so good.
This is not happening.
Oh, wait.
Please open your mouth.
Oh my god.
Oy, oy, oy.
Scary.
Maybe we wait with the fight club, actually, until we've taken on the boss.
There's a 21% chance of an angel.
That's not too bad.
That was masterful.
It really was.
I mean, I'm not here to toot my own horn, but that was pretty fucking good.
Actually, I am here to toot my own horn.
That's the only thing I'm doing.
Love to toot toot.
Fuck this!
I mean, what do you do?
This is impossible to avoid.
Freaking impossible.
Line up, line up.
Okay, he still does his gravity shit.
And the boss is here.
This is, uh, my chance to get an angel again.
Oh god, oh god.
Holy crap!
You like farts?
Fly through my farts.
Yeah.
Stay mad.
That was actually phenomenal.
And we get angel!
Oh hey!
Sick!
Delirious.
Uh, summons...
I don't like this one.
I'm gonna re-roll.
Seven seals.
Meh.
Ugh.
Fucking terrible items.
What is going on here?
I hate this.
Alright, whatever.
Let's blow this guy up.
One here, one down here.
Line up.
Get farted on!
Okay.
Oh crap.
Oh wow.
Dude, how do- How am I supposed to know which direction?
He's gonna shoot these fucking lasers.
There's no way to know.
Ugh.
Fuck off already.
Poof.
Okay, so maybe I need to make sure that I take this on the same character.
Uh, I think I had it with this guy.
Yeah, we got the key now.
If I want to do that later.
And I may want to do that later.
Let's see here.
We still have Fight Club and a couple rooms we didn't clear.
Let's go do that.
There's a chance we get something amazing.
Remember last time I backtracked?
I got the most amazing thing ever.
Ah, we gotta be full HP here.
Check it out.
We're gonna- Oh, I can't even grab it from here.
Oh, damn.
That ain't good.
Oh my god.
Hey, at least it's Jacob getting hit.
I'm actually happy about that.
I'm even gonna go in here.
Ah, well, that was a mistake.
Let's go find some healing.
I mean, I guess I could bomb the stuff up here in this room.
You know, I could bomb these and then get in, but I'm gonna end up losing...
If I'm fast enough, I could maybe do it.
Let me think.
So I put one here.
Wait, no.
Do this first.
Here.
There.
And then we...
What do we do?
We go up and to the right.
Up and to the right.
Okay.
Alright.
Um, so now you stay all the way over here.
Spawn some...
Two of hearts!
Um...
Two of hearts.
Nice!
And then judgment.
Um...
Here.
Ah!
Fuck.
This may not be worth it.
Ah, sh...
Yeah, this is...
This was bad.
Can we get HP somehow?
There's a shop, right?
Maybe there was HP in that shop I can buy.
Could also blow this guy up.
And look for a secret at the same time.
Too bad.
Uh...
That...
Box...
I'm not gonna open it.
Too risky.
I could blow up some skulls.
Maybe something good happens.
Maybe combine it with looking for...
A secret.
Except I'm not gonna be able to hit the skulls and find secrets here.
Fuck it.
Sick!
Very nice.
Oh my god, steep sail!
And healing!
Yes!
Glorious.
Yeah, that was a heart, baby!
Very good.
I think I'll get the starter deck.
Starter deck and...
What was this one?
Oh, oh, the pillars range up.
Ooh, uh, yeah.
Nice.
And this one was battery pack.
Fully recharges the health active item on pickup.
Spawns two to four random battery pickups.
I mean, that's not good right now.
It was good earlier, I guess.
Maybe, if I could...
Or if I wanted to re-roll something.
I think I'll take the starter deck.
Judgment.
I think I'll buy this one too.
Yeah.
Hermit.
I mean, I'll take that.
Okay.
That was very nice going back here.
I'm actually not done.
I actually really like the fact that I get double bombs.
That's sweet.
Okay.
Let's get out of here.
Yep.
Okay.
We gotta be careful with Jacob because one hit and Angel is gone.
We're most likely gonna lose the Angel.
Fatty needs to be in the front.
This is also the mom floor.
Oh, man.
No.
And there she blows.
Just like that.
It's all over.
Unfortunate.
Wow.
Oh, ho, ho.
We can re-roll now.
Kind of want to make a sick play here, but I think it's a little too sick.
Even for me.
Okay, you ready?
This is gonna be insane.
Watch this shit.
Let me think.
I click and then I go...
Right.
Fuck!
You gotta aim for the stars, right?
You gotta aim for the stars sometimes.
It didn't work out this time, though.
Dude, what the...
Why is Jacob the only one taking damage?
For fuck's sake!
Why is Fat Guy not getting hit...
Once?
Fuckin' hell!
No!
Come on!
Okay, we got the heart at least.
Fat Guy in first.
Okay, that's not great.
I'm...
Scared of that.
And they should stay down, right?
Okay.
Oh, there's nothing else in here.
Oh, man.
I don't even know what the plan is.
Oh, ho.
Fat Guy in front.
No, don't do this to me.
I guess I could open it with...
Yisao.
I think it may be worth it.
Honestly.
Strength.
Ooh.
I like.
No, no.
Wrong button.
I meant to do the other one.
How do I do the other one?
It's fine.
I've got five coins.
Still no treasure room.
Let's find it.
You know what?
Oh, we have one bomb left.
That chest can...
Go away.
You're dead?
You're not dead.
There we go.
Okay.
Five coins.
Oh, wait.
This is not a shop.
Adrenaline.
What?
Increases Isaac's damage for each empty red heart container he currently has.
Right.
So that would have to go to...
Jacob.
I forgot I could re-roll.
Motherfucker.
I mean, it's not a bad item, but...
I forgot.
That was a forgetty spaghetti.
Sometimes that meal happens, you know?
And you gotta eat it.
Wow!
Coupon...
Oh, dude.
I want coupon.
We gotta scrounge up a couple coins.
Maybe from this guy.
Maybe look for a secret as well down here.
No coins?
Boo!
Keep exploring.
Just stay at range.
Come at me.
Nice!
Thank you, helper.
Little guy on your steed.
Ho-ho-ho-ho!
Man.
Oh!
Look at this one!
I'm gonna blow up both.
Open your mouth.
The fool.
Do we want to go home?
We actually have the option to do this.
Let me think.
If we go home, we cannot use the key we made.
Because the key is made for the Satan area.
I don't know.
I'll keep it, though.
Just in case.
Oh, God.
Oh, the fucking creep!
Okay, we're about done here.
We didn't find the money, so I'm gonna have to blow up the donation machine.
Again.
I just value this run too much.
We can't let this one slip through our fingers.
I'm sorry to say.
I need this item.
Let's also make a bomb over here, then.
Um...
Let me think.
Give it...
So, wait.
If I give this to Jacob...
And then I switch...
Yeah.
Then we switch this one.
And then I re-roll.
Little baggy.
Isaac can hold two pills at once.
All future cart drops are replaced with pills.
Okay.
Sounds good.
Please, health up.
Health up.
Health up!
Yeah!
What the fuck?
Why is it...
Wait, what?
Nice.
Why did I have two of them?
Wait, what the hell?
I don't know why I just had two of them.
But here we go.
He actually has more damage now because he has missing health, right?
I could try this again.
One last attempt.
Maybe I leave one over here.
Okay, one last!
Yes!
Nice.
Good stuff.
We just have this guy.
I can blow up.
That's too risky.
Okay, you actually.
Here, have some money.
Please give me like a full health item.
Wow, really?
The parts are gonna be essential here.
Guys, I'm actually gonna let you guys decide.
Are we gonna go home?
Because we have the opportunity to.
Never mind.
We don't.
I don't have the full card.
Never mind.
We don't have an option.
Fuck.
I was gonna let you guys decide whether or not we went home or we went downstairs, you know?
She's doing stairs.
Yes.
Yeah.
They're making it go out.
I can't stop thinking about it.
Give me the negative.
And then?
And then we go.
What happened to my full card?
Fucking hell.
It just disappeared.
Scarred womb?
Isn't that a new one?
I don't think I've seen this one before.
What the hell is this?
Oh god.
Oh god!
We got desynced there.
That was bad.
Oh!
I'm gonna pick this up later.
And we're gonna give it to Ezow, actually.
This is gonna be a bad one.
Nope, we're good.
Let's go left first.
Aha!
I mean, how am I even supposed to dodge that one?
Come on, now.
That is just chaotic.
We lost the angel.
Again.
Let's not forget, we have reroll.
Oh, but wait a minute.
The coupon is useless now.
There's no shops here.
Bruh.
Why did I take that?
I don't like that, either.
What?
Am I...
Oh, it's the creep.
Oh man, it's getting a little tough.
This is gonna be a tough going, I can tell you.
Get pooped on!
Bartmaster 3000.
Actually, uh...
Jacob goes first.
Oh no.
Hey, check it out.
I have an idea.
We're gonna stand next to him like this.
Oh, okay, he died.
He has to fire tooth shots.
Um...
Yeah.
Whoa!
Not good, not good.
Are we done in here?
We're done in here.
Jacob first.
No.
I'm honestly surprised I even got this far with this character.
Boss is here.
I think I might just have to do it.
Alright, bring it on.
Oh god.
Oh, what the fuck was that?
Oh, he's shooting bombs.
I don't know what I'm getting hit by.
No, I need healing.
Uh, I guess I'll take this.
But, I mean...
No, that's just like...
That's like a shit item for me.
But I guess it is giving me speed.
Oh man, I don't like this at all.
I'm gonna re-roll!
I can still re-roll.
Okay!
Ease out.
Wait, no, no.
I come back and re-roll again.
I want full healing.
Or something.
I'm not feeling good about this.
Are we both flying?
No, only one of us is flying.
Oh, that's actually interesting.
That's gonna...
desync us really hard, I think.
If I'm not careful.
This is not good.
I feel like I'm cooked.
This is...
This is really bad.
Oh my god, oh my god!
We're desynced!
Fucking gravity bastards.
Nice.
Get behind him.
Oh no, not this.
Wow!
Fuck me.
Jesus.
Give me healing!
Oh no, this is...
This is bad.
This is bad!
What?
How?
How am I doing it?
We have full charge!
Go back and re-roll.
Pill!
Oh, minus one luck is bad.
Actually, let's take this now.
Up, up, up.
Oh god.
Careful not to step on these.
Oh, that's not gonna help me very much.
I'm in deep shit, guys.
I need healing.
This is...
This is looking real rough.
Fat guy in front.
I also have a hermit.
Wait, I have a hermit.
I could've gone home.
I've had this card the entire time.
I cannot believe it.
What a blunder.
Jesus Christ.
What the hell is this?
It's a money machine thingy.
Haha, that's kinda cool, actually.
I dig that.
More health.
Health.
Healing.
But what am I gonna do with all this money if I'm dead?
Haha, look at Esau, the little fat devil.
Look at that guy.
He looks so cute.
I just wanna squish his cheeks.
Oh god.
Can we please just...
Align here?
Oh no, not the eyes!
Oh, what's happening?
Okay, good, good, good.
That's not an enemy.
It's a friend.
Okay.
Poo.
Hoi yoi yoi.
Wow, the dodges!
We're off the charts, I gotta say.
We got inanimate objects.
My worst enemy.
Good.
Oh my god.
We can re-roll again.
Nothing to re-roll, though.
Boss!
71% angel!
Guys!
Are you ready?
Wish me luck.
There's no way we're not getting hit here.
The halo!
Tears, damage, range, plus one health.
Uh, Esau, I guess?
Uh, let me see.
Tears.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Esau.
But, uh, I could also re-roll.
It's a good one.
Uh, I'm gonna re-roll.
Uh, I don't care about the angel.
Or do I care about the angel?
Maybe I care.
No, I don't care.
I don't care.
Also, I should have given that to Esau.
I fucked up.
Um, we're gonna go down.
Okay, so now we gotta use the key.
As soon as we see the door.
There's one more somewhere.
There you are.
I'm gonna save that battery.
It's still shooting.
I don't care about that key.
Oh, I dodged it!
Are the projectiles still there?
No, okay.
Uh, give it to Esau.
Gotta balance the HP here.
No thanks.
Curse of the Lost is not good.
Oh, wait.
I'm okay.
I'm- I'm- I'm- Okay.
I'm in a fucking corner.
Get out of the corner.
Oi, oi, oi.
Wow.
No enemies?
Oh, don't take that.
We're gonna save those batteries.
Oh, nice.
Uh, I can fly.
Get a key as well.
I'm surprised we're still in this run.
Honestly, I thought this would have been over a long time ago.
Look at this little guy.
Go here.
Oh, these cannot be shot.
Okay.
And we got some flames.
Wait.
I'm gonna do the same thing here.
Very sick.
Keep clearing.
I wanna find an item that I can reroll, man.
Oh, that's nice.
Boss here.
Ah, but wait a minute.
Uh, hold on.
So this is like...
Oh, uh...
I'm actually not sure.
I don't remember, man.
I don't remember what the fuck is going on in this level.
I hope this is actually the level I think it is.
Oh, wait.
I can destroy these.
Like, I hope it's the one where I actually get to use my key I've gotten from the angels.
That green stuff is not good for me.
Uh, brain worm?
Oh, that's actually exciting.
I'll take it.
Yeah, fuck the secret room.
Ah, yeah.
Okay, so...
Oh, wait.
This is...
Oh, fuck.
This is delirium, isn't it?
Fuck, that's not even what I wanted to do.
Aw, man.
Piss!
That's fine, though.
We're gonna teach him a lesson.
Wanna come over here?
Wait, he gets blocked by the jars?
Interesting.
I'm gonna reroll this.
Okay.
Not bad.
Let's give that to...
Ysau.
And then we're gonna go get some batteries.
How about wait?
No!
That's crazy.
Oh, man.
We had some more batteries in the big room.
But we don't need them now.
We can wait a bit.
I just gotta hope we don't get delirium fast, you know?
Oh, crap.
Curse of the tower.
Yikes.
I'll be back in...
I'm gonna change that for sure.
Let's get that battery.
Hopefully it's not the one that's floating in an island.
Oh, no.
I can make a hole.
Or a bridge, I mean.
Take the small one first.
Can I?
Damn it.
Okay, well.
I'm gonna go back and reroll.
Not too bad.
More HP.
Can't be helpful.
Let's go say hi to this boss up here.
Actually, let's wait until we have some battery.
Any more batteries?
Nope.
Not here.
Oh, what is this?
Oh, that was the shitty pill.
No interest in that.
Inanimate objects!
That was actually so well played.
I'm proud of myself.
Oh, battery!
Big one!
And then I can grab it later.
I don't want to waste that full battery on...
my current levels here.
Okay.
Fully charged.
Let's go deal with the boss.
See if we can't reroll to something nice.
Hopefully it's not delirium.
I need all your thoughts and prayers right now.
Thoughts and prayers.
I need them.
Nice!
Let's just fart it up in the center.
Like this.
Step into my office.
Wait, what is that?
Why can't I see what it is?
Oh.
Oh, no!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Yes!
That's okay.
I like it.
I could also reroll.
But I think I like this one.
Yeah, I'll take it.
Okay.
Now we find another boss.
We get the battery first.
No, actually we don't.
We find the boss first.
And then if we haven't gotten any battery, then we get the battery.
The bouncing tears are kind of nice.
Wait, what?
Oh.
Oh my god.
Wow.
Is that a ghost bomb?
What the hell is that?
I've never seen that.
Good.
Uh, that's for you.
Had to happen.
At least the pain is over with.
That was nice.
Okay, we got a boss here.
Thoughts and prayers.
Fuck!
Okay.
Now I really need your thoughts and your prayers.
Mom?
He's turning into an angel.
There he goes, angeling again.
I like the big open space though.
That's nice.
Where is he?
My damage output is not great here.
Oh god.
I don't like my current situation!
Shit.
Man, that was a mindfuck just now.
What the hell are you doing now?
Is he invisible?
Fucking hell.
This guy needs to calm the shit down!
Umbilical?
What even is that fetal protection?
Whatever you say.
Oh my god!
Yeah, I don't know.
I'm dying here.
There it is, baby!
There it is!
I was locking in so hard.
Whew!
We take that.
Wow.
Suplex has appeared.
Okay.
I don't know if that's good or not.
I guess we'll find out.
I gotta take a quick piss and I'll be back.
Win streak of two!
Okay.
Guys, I need a win streak of three.
I gotta go for it.
Um, the question is with who.
Um, let me see.
Wait a second.
We have never gone home with a Seisel!
We don't have the little page.
Notice.
I mean, we have gone home, obviously, and gotten the alternate version.
But we haven't actually beat the boss, I don't think.
You see that?
There's no page.
Wait, we got the page on this guy?
What the hell?
Yeah, I'm gonna do it.
I- I gotta get to three!
My boy is Seisel!
It's been a while, my friend.
How are you doing?
How are you- Watch me be super lucky, by the way, immediately.
Do you just leave Crete where they land?
Uh, yeah, okay.
But how does that work for me?
Okay.
So I can go like this, and it'll form a little path, I guess.
Precharge.
We're going home.
And we're gonna beat the beast.
Wow, we can re-roll in here.
Why does that always happen when I don't have any money?
I gotta get used to playing with the laser again here.
Good.
Man, I forgot how powerful this laser is.
Are you gonna jump towards me or what?
Come on, jump!
Thank god I didn't blow up this machine.
Maybe I'll need it later.
Also, we have the fool immediately, so we can...
Pretty much guaranteed go home.
As long as I don't drop it or do something stupid.
Yeah.
Uh, no.
Go here.
Just stay down here.
Nice and safe.
Famine.
Okay.
Actually, not a big fan of this man.
Nice!
Clean!
Oh, not the cube of meat!
Anything but that.
Okay, well...
I'll roll with it.
Uh, I haven't finished exploring.
Wow!
Bro had no chance.
Okay, time for secrets.
I think there may be one here.
We're gonna mega confirm this.
Looks good to me.
Yep.
Ay-yi-yi-yi-yi-yi-yi-yi-yi-yi!
That's nice.
Let's check out the shop now.
21 coins!
Remember when I said I never have coins to re-roll?
Today's not that day.
I don't want any of this.
We're gonna re-roll.
Okay, the heart is good.
Maybe a bit more re-roll.
Or I'll blow it up.
Let's blow it up.
Night light.
Ooh, that is good!
That is good!
I want this.
It also looks nice.
Makes me feel more safe.
Also donate a bit to this thing.
Card?
Strength?
No, I need the full.
Could blow it up.
No, let's save that.
I'm saving my bombs.
I feel the win streak of three coming, guys.
I'm playing so slow and meticulous.
I'm not gonna let any advantage go by my nose.
Adrenaline.
Hold on, this is actually useless for me.
Completely useless.
We're gonna wait with that in case we somehow get an option to re-roll it.
I...
Probably...
It's not gonna happen, but...
Maybe, right?
Nah...
That is pathetic.
How did I let this happen?
A little spider like that got the best of me.
No.
I'm poor.
Nice!
God, I love this character so much.
I've missed it.
I've missed you, buddy.
I really have.
I haven't even looked for Tinted Rocks.
Yeah.
Good clings.
Damn.
Not a great item, but...
It's decent, I guess.
Uh, I think I'm gonna go Angel, honestly.
Yeah.
It's Angel time.
Would love to grab that blue heart.
Somehow.
Trust we're gonna find a shit ton of money.
In that room up there.
Hey!
Huge!
Wait, what's this?
Faded Polaroid!
Can be used to open a strange door as well?
Wait, doesn't that mean I don't even have to fight Mom, technically?
I can just go.
I mean, I wanna fight Mom, obviously.
For the reward.
But, you know.
Wait, does that mean I can keep the Faded Polaroid?
And consume that on the door?
And then keep the other Polaroid I pick up, or what?
To keep the damage bonus.
Because if that's the case, that sounds pretty good.
I don't wanna go in there, actually.
Nah, I'm gonna keep my blue heart.
Maybe look for a secret, though.
Maybe up here.
Looks good so far.
Yeah.
Beautiful.
That's exactly what I need.
Oh, man.
I actually like this more than the Polaroid.
Let's blow these fuckers up.
No, I only got one of them?
Alright, fine.
Maybe this will lead us to riches.
It should be a 50% increase in total coins, right?
Statistically.
Oh, yeah.
We've killed the boss already.
Let's go.
So far, so good.
33% Angel.
Lovely.
Playing it safe here.
Empty heart.
Oh, I forgot about that other item I could pick up.
For every missing heart container, I gain damage or something.
So, at the start of each floor, grant one red health if the floor was entered with one red HP or less.
Wait, what?
I don't understand this.
I'll find out.
Come on, then.
Sweet.
I could go in there, actually.
What?
I wasn't even near it!
That is bullshit.
I wasn't even touching that at all.
That's crazy.
Boss?
The frail.
Oh my god, what?
Of all the places he could appear, you know?
Underwear.
Hey, range is good for me.
It's really good.
No Angel, though.
That's very unlucky.
Next floor, though, right?
Next floor.
Oh, you can feel the range difference here.
Oh, that's nice.
I'm tempted to buy the pill.
Yeah!
Hehehehe.
I am the master of pilling.
I'm a pill maxer.
I will be signing autographs after this session.
Don't pick that up, actually.
Oh, he's camouflaged!
Wait, am I revealing him with the flashlight?
Hey, that's cool!
I didn't know the flashlight did that.
Oh, and an eternal heart as well.
That's dope.
Oh, wait, I can fly.
Heh!
Right.
The hermit.
Uh, nah.
Wait, that's a library!
I haven't seen one of those in ten years.
That's sweet.
Two books.
Anarchist cookbook and...
Ah, too bad.
I thought it was the one that gave me black hearts.
Um, yeah.
Okay.
I still like this one, though.
When this guy wants keys, he can fuck off.
I don't know what to deal with these enemies that have, like, a weird color.
I still don't understand what that means.
Let's not forget about the eternal heart before we leave.
Okay.
Fight club!
Yes, sir.
Oh, that's a lot of money!
More money!
What's going on with my money?
And my penny is going crazy right now because of it.
That's amazing.
What a great fight club that was.
We can go to the shop and go nuts now!
Let's do it!
I'm taking this.
32 coins, man.
And I had nothing when I came here.
I actually don't want anything here.
Ooh.
Hey, this sucks!
I can donate.
You know what?
Let's donate.
For a good cause, right?
I've been taking so much lately.
It's time to give back to the community.
There we go.
Fully donated.
That should make up for my past sins.
And then some.
I think we're done here.
Right?
This run has been textbook smooth AF.
No complaints.
Dankeschön!
Like a deer in the headlights.
Ahaha!
You're not fooling me.
I'm not falling for that.
What is that?
Boiled baby.
I'm not excited.
But it's okay.
Very good.
Getting so many extra coins because of the penny.
Feels amazing.
I think we do this now.
Come on, Angel!
I need you.
Let's use this book.
Wow, that did a lot.
Holy shit!
That really helped.
More range!
Huge!
And Angel!
Oh no, it's the shit item.
What is this?
I hate it.
Asshole.
He ran into the fire.
Yeah, keep running into the fire, dummy.
Dude, he's very tanky for some reason.
You know, give me this one.
Let's activate it.
Need to go deeper.
Wait, what?
Oh, that was a shovel?
Interesting.
Let's not accidentally walk on that.
That was a tough Angel.
Holy crap!
But wait, I actually don't need this.
I needed to go home and...
Yeah, I needed to go home.
I don't know why I'm doing this.
Oh well.
That's fine.
Let's go back.
That was definitely some wasted HP.
Didn't need to do any of that.
Shit.
I took a gamble there because I didn't remember what the thingies looked like on the other side.
Oh, nice.
Hey!
Huge!
I mean, small.
That was my last key as well.
Can you believe that shit?
I accidentally ran into it.
That's crazy.
Oh, nice.
Okay.
Watch this.
Bring them all together.
Efficiency, people.
Receive a...
Wait, what?
Rules card?
Receive a gameplay hint.
Huh?
Some doors...
Shit game!
Honestly, dude.
Why the fuck is that not paused?
I'll review the vault.
Fucking leave the text on screen, man.
Until I click a button or something.
Game design 101.
I think I may have enough money at this point that I can take this.
Yeah.
Exactly 15.
Oh, no.
It's a fake shop.
Hate the fake shops.
Another fool!
You know what that means, right?
I think you know what that means, because I know what that means.
You ready?
This way.
We can afford to go into the curse room.
Hold on now.
That's kind of exciting.
I like it.
And no more.
Fool out of here.
We grab the other fool.
Not yet, though.
When we leave.
Do I go in here?
No, no, no.
Thank you.
I think I'm done.
Time to leave.
There's a fight room, though, but I can't really...
I don't understand these.
Wait.
Maybe it's because you need to not have defeated the boss for that to be open.
Imagine.
Maybe you gotta do it before the boss.
Right?
I gotta check that.
Okay, it's not mom yet.
Gotta play it safe.
Bullshit statues.
Ruining my day.
The sun.
Reveal it.
I'm gonna bomb this.
Library!
You know what that means?
Conjoined.
The bible.
Telepathy.
Satanic bible!
Come to daddy.
That's what I needed.
Massive.
Massive!
This is like a...
An assasal wet dream right now.
Oh no!
Wait, it's bookworm.
Not conjoined.
Yeah, right.
So wait.
Does that mean I'm actually sometimes shooting two beams or...?
Maybe that does nothing for me.
Also, um...
Telepathy...
Yeah.
I could bring the bible to mom.
Just for that one boss.
Right?
Wouldn't be a bad idea.
A bomb.
He wants bombs.
No.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Another book!
What is it with these books?
Necromonicon?
I don't care.
Can I...
Can I get in here without...
God!
I feel like every single tragedy you can dream up in this game, I've experienced it, you know?
Uh...
No, I don't like that.
Pill.
Capricorn!
Speed, Tears, Damage, Range, Health.
Ooh, that's really nice.
That's just solid.
Yike!
Much appreciated.
Come at me then!
Easy peasy, Lemon Squeezy.
Little Gish.
Familiar that fire, Solving Tears.
I'm just gonna solve my equations.
I could give him some bombs.
Just a few.
Item me!
Come on!
Bro!
That was not worth it.
Little bastard ripped me off.
I do have some money I can use here.
Speaking of, we gotta go to the shop!
Let's go do that.
Hey, real talk.
If I see a demon room, I'm taking it because I want to turn all my red hearts into demon items.
Hmm?
Very nice.
That was satisfying!
So was that!
Cool.
I'm gonna blow up some skulls.
It's gonna bring me to 3 out of 3 on Yes Mother, but I don't really care about that, honestly.
Fuck that.
Black can't- Ooh!
Oh!
I like that one.
That's a W.
Discounted.
You have to spawn a coin?
No thanks.
Nah.
No, I need the fool.
May as well do it.
Turn them all into black hearts, right?
Then grab the other two.
Actually, we're not even done clearing.
Wait, there's a room over here that we didn't clear.
Definitely want to clear that.
Dude, I'm playing so fucking well today!
It's insane!
I'm on another level!
I cannot be stopped!
I'm a Binding of Isaac Master.
Get me up after for lessons.
I charge $900 every half hour.
For this wisdom that I will impart upon you.
A goat hoof!
Some extra speed.
Oh, that's a- Oh, okay.
It's a trinket.
I'm less excited now.
Then again, maybe I am excited.
Because, check it out.
The current one I have...
Increased chance of finding soul hearts, black hearts, and bone hearts.
Whatever bone hearts are.
I don't even know what that is.
Anyway, this is not really that important because I have the satanic bible now.
So, having a bit of extra speed?
Not too bad!
Flawless argument.
Logic, 100%.
Also, totally worth going in here.
Dead cat.
Oh, wait, wait, wait.
Grants nine extra lives, but reduces red heart containers to one.
Okay, so hold up!
This is only gonna reduce my red hearts, right?
It's not gonna fuck up my other hearts.
So, this may actually be worth it.
Do I have to choose?
Oh, nice!
Okay, use the item.
Wait, three out of three on Guppy?
Guppy's hairball.
Whoa!
Challenge eight!
Nice!
Very nice.
I don't know what the Guppy thing does.
What does it do?
I have no idea.
Oh well.
Let's get out of here!
Next floor.
Actually, there's a battery somewhere.
No, there's not.
I'm lying.
Dude, nine lives with all these eggs.
Here we go!
Forty-six percent angel.
Oh, wait!
I have a little, uh, Guppy thing following me.
That's what that is.
But what does it do?
Is it shooting, or?
What is it doing?
I'm not sure.
It must be doing something nice.
Oh, look at this.
So watch!
The fool?
Yeah.
It's always the fool.
I think it's confirmed at this point.
Like, beyond any reasonable doubt.
Uh, yeah.
Mom's purse.
Two trinkets at the same time!
I do like that.
Let's come back with more money.
One more coin.
Surely we can scrounge that up somewhere.
Also, why do I have so many flies on me?
Is that maybe related to the Guppy thing?
Weird.
Maybe a ways to do that, I'm not sure.
Hey, we actually have another fool, so we can actually go inside that curse room.
You know what?
I like this!
Am I crazy?
Wait, do I like it?
I like this.
More black hearts for me!
Dim bulb?
Uh, nah.
Giant cell.
Yeah, whatever.
Arcade.
I need one more coin!
Okay, so wait.
Here's the boss.
We could just do it now, I guess.
Yeah.
Come on, then.
Damn, I have damage!
What the frick?
The damage, though!
What's out of control?
Uh, Abaddon.
Damage.
Oh, oh!
Wait, wait, wait.
Uh, Replace is all.
Yeah, okay, that's probably good as well.
Chance of fire fear.
Yeah, I mean, that's good.
That's good.
Little horn.
Don't care about that.
Gimme.
Abso-fucking-lutely.
Could I even take this?
Honestly, at this point, I think we're good.
Uh, I take it.
Yes, we're gonna be lower on hearts here, but it's okay, we're gonna get them back.
Alright, so we're not done exploring.
We need batteries.
There's my money!
Man, what is this little guppy thing doing?
I need to pay attention to it.
It must be doing something.
Gimme that one.
Golden horseshoe.
Well, are we gonna have any more treasure rooms?
I don't think so.
I guess we'll take it for now.
Wasn't there another trinket that I left behind?
I think there is, down here.
That one, I guess, but it's not really needed.
I could use the fool in here.
Sick.
Arcade.
Why not?
Let's have a look.
Man, that's disappointing.
Blow him up.
I like pills.
Shit.
That was not good.
That's a noticeably slower charge, you know?
Okay.
But it's okay, though.
I think it's time we leave.
Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa!
Don't go there, don't go there!
I almost went the wrong way!
Jesus Christ.
Okay, nothing else we need to do.
We are good.
Let's go.
The beast shall die.
Eat that candy.
Puke your guts out.
Oh, I can't get in there.
What was that sound just now?
What happened?
Dude, I think Guppy is doing something with these flies.
Like, I have so many.
Puberty, nice.
Ha, he stepped on the spikes.
Dummy.
Okay, so this door is still closed even before I dealt with the boss.
So, it's not the boss.
That determines that.
Wait, what?
Oh, he's static.
Okay, he's not gonna do anything.
Those enemies I just killed reminds me of the back rooms a little bit.
Still life.
I'm thinking, though.
Let's say I didn't have any red hearts.
Is my nine lives then useless?
You know?
Because if I spawn...
And I...
No, actually, I don't know what would happen.
Maybe just die if that happens.
I could go in there.
I'm gonna do it.
Perthro!
That was a long shot.
Oh my god!
That was fast.
Demon's tail!
80% of drop hearts are replaced with keys.
All heart drops become black hearts.
No thanks.
And again.
Actually, yes.
How do I change my...
Wait, I want speed.
And I want this.
Jim, Jim, Jim, Jim.
Perthro.
Those guys are scary.
Free lemonade or question mark?
I would like question mark.
I could also reroll.
God's flesh?
Chance to fire tears that temporarily shrink enemies.
Shrunken enemies attempt to flee and can be crushed by walking...
I don't like that.
I'm taking this.
Number one.
Tears up, range down?
That's terrible.
That's horrible.
That really fucked me just now.
This is gonna be bad, guys.
Definitely one of the worst ones.
But I'm feeling good, nonetheless.
I think we just go.
I spent it.
It's gone.
Just get over it.
What do you mean?
How could you have spent our savings?
Okay, so what is this?
Death?
Yeah!
Get that range back!
Lovely.
Watch me find a key in this run when I don't need one.
I guarantee it.
Thing is, though, do I even care about clearing if I don't want to look for the key?
I don't think I do.
I just go.
Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait!
I keep gaining an empty heart!
Oh, I don't like this!
It's because of that item I have!
No, it's gonna eat into my blacks!
Oh, no!
Can we somehow stop that?
I don't like that at all.
Oh, well, that's not gonna do much.
This one is a fake.
I should have used my thing afterwards, damn it.
Whatever.
Look, I'm gonna get...
Yeah, I'm gonna get another red heart now.
Disturbed, just like his father.
I don't like that!
Look at who he has to look up to!
I think you're drunk again, aren't you?
Shut up, Maggie!
You just keep pushing me like this!
I'm leaving!
Good, please!
Keep yabbering and yabbering!
You'll be fine without you!
Abandon us like you abandoned yourself!
Lovely.
Ah, why did I reuse it?
For some reason, I thought I had lost an HP.
I'm gonna get too many red hearts, guys.
This is...
There's so many levels here where I go up, you know?
The fool.
We're gonna have like eight red hearts or so when we're done here.
Eat my money.
Did you hear how you sound?
Pray with me.
Pray for your salvation.
Come, pray with us, Isaac.
Oh, wait.
What happened to my other perthro?
Oh, I used it, right?
Yeah.
True.
Hey, this one is good for me!
I like that.
More damage.
Oh, damn.
I like the way the music ramps up.
The flies are doing a lot of damage.
Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait.
I only gain red hearts if I have one or less.
That's how that works.
I get it now.
Wait, what?
You know what?
I like it.
Let's just try that.
It's fun.
I guess I'll have to pay attention in the bottom left what kind of trinket I have.
But I don't recognize this trinket that I have right now.
What is that?
How do I...
Oh, no.
I can't even see it.
Oh, some tears.
Okay.
Hey, you want keys?
I got keys for you.
Range is good, thanks.
Careful not to pick up the wrong thing here.
Oh, crap.
Okay, no more.
Not much money.
Lock up, tears down.
Oh, no.
That's fine.
Could be worse.
Take me up.
I'm so happy it's not going to keep giving me red hearts right now.
I feel like it's going to be easy.
Like, I'm going to fucking dominate this right now.
The sun is amazing.
Is it, though?
No.
Yes, it is, because I have some red hearts.
It is actually amazing.
It is amazing.
I could re-roll this.
I could get the per throw and re-roll.
But extra range is good for me, so I think I'm going to take this.
Yeah.
Let's do it!
I'm going to be teaching you a lesson.
What the...
Dude, what the fuck?!
I'm being taught a lesson here, it seems.
Jesus.
Good damage.
Very good damage.
That is beautiful.
That is wonderful.
Let's go.
I've got the sun.
Oh no, wait.
This is a funky trinket we have right now.
I don't hate it.
It's okay.
Oh god.
Awkward as hell!
I don't like this!
What's with these fucking projectiles?!
Oh god!
Oh no, I don't have range now.
Okay, I can actually go through it.
It's fine, it's fine.
Everything's cool.
That was bad.
Why am I getting hit?
Wait, you could destroy those projectiles?
I just destroyed one of those things he threw.
The Titanic Bible is not actually that great here.
Stop that.
Good.
Here we go, here we go.
I've got bombs for your ass.
Oh shit, I bombed myself.
Okay.
Oh god.
Oh no, no, no, no.
Oh, he's gonna suck me in.
No, no, no.
Not happening.
No way, Jose.
Oh, maybe it is happening.
The sun!
There
it is, baby!
That's three!
Lil Abaddon has appeared.
Boom!
Guys, we gotta do one more.
But I gotta take a piss first.
Be right back.
Okay.
Next up, we're gonna do...
Uh, let me see.
Let me see, let me see, let me see, let me see.
We could do Eden, and...
Um, let me see.
Wait, we haven't even killed, uh, Isaac with Judas, it seems.
We have killed Satan.
We could try Judas.
That's a tough one, though.
That's one HP guy.
I think I'm gonna do it.
Um, guys, I'm gonna ask you right now.
It is correct that the downwards, uh, cross, that's not Isaac, right?
Isaac is the normal cross.
Hold on.
Isaac is the normal cross, right?
Okay, good.
I just don't want to waste an entire run on something I could easily just check in a VOD right now, and I don't want to check it.
Thank you.
So I am going to go Judas.
That's the plan.
I'm prepared to lose my streak right now, it's fine.
The important thing is, we got to win streak three, and it was a glorious streak.
I'm proud of it.
Gonna be weird not having a laser now.
Oh no.
Not a good start.
I need some healing.
Oy yoy yoy.
Oh no.
I'm not a big fan of this.
Actually, I'm fine.
They're gonna trickle out a little bit at a time here.
Come on.
There we go.
Okay.
Oy shio.
Oy.
God damn, son.
Oh no.
Oy.
Shia.
Oh my god.
God damn.
Uh, he's a 10% chance to heal.
Have a red heart.
Okay, but I need that chance right now.
I need that to come into effect.
Compound fracture?
Range replaces tears with bone shots that shatter into bone fragments.
They deal half Isaac's tear damage to enemies struck.
Oh, the bone fragments.
I like it.
I'm like the skeletons now.
Oh, this is bad.
Maybe.
Holy shit.
Shop?
Come on, let me buy a heart.
Blue heart.
Okay, blue heart.
Nice.
Oh, I need that.
Much needed.
Let me see.
I think we just go for boss.
Famine.
This guy's tough.
Nice.
Oh god.
No, not this.
Not the bandit.
Oh, nice.
Okay, we're back.
Huge.
Wait, what?
Oh, it's a double wombo combo.
Oh, no.
That means there's another treasure room.
I'm not ready for this.
Holy crap.
Oh no, this is, this is, I'm dead.
Maybe.
This room is killer!
Oh god.
Okay, I think we're safe.
Wow.
Okay.
That's messed up.
Let's find the other treasure room.
More spiders.
Goddamn spiders.
Yes, dude!
We healed a little bit.
Wait, did that matter at all?
I'm not sure.
The wafer!
Okay, we're getting out of here now.
Fuck this.
We're leaving.
Massive item.
We can't take damage during this boss fight though, because we gotta keep the eternal heart.
Please, dear god, let it be an easy one.
Light it over.
Oh, this one is...
It's, it's okay.
Thank god.
Old bandage.
Yes.
Oh, that's so good.
That's so good.
This is so huge, guys.
This is a great start.
I smell a streak of four coming.
Awesome.
Dude,
this room is kind of insane.
Oh my god.
Rainbow.
Let's not destroy that.
We also have gold poop.
Wait, I didn't mean to...
Oh, it was the fragments.
Oh man.
This thing again.
Okay.
Not that bad.
So much poop here.
Oh my god.
Dude, why is he so fast?
Sick.
Imagine a health up though.
Are you imagining it?
Now multiply that by two.
That's how I would have felt.
If I'd gotten health up.
Dude, I'm in the zone today.
Holy shit.
Can I kill this guy?
Okay, I can.
He looked like one of those that I can't kill until I kill the other ones, you know?
The skeletal things are gonna be nice in here.
The way it, you know, sprinkles all... all over.
Here we...
Nice.
We still have 100% demon.
I'm even considering demons and not angels, just because we got so much HP, you know?
But I think we should focus on the angels.
That's very nice.
Oh, they're so fast.
Oh god.
Run into the fire.
Your daddy's on fire.
Would love more options.
Wait, how did this guy down here die just now?
He just sort of disappeared.
No, not this guy.
I'm gonna jump.
I know you want to jump.
Even more range.
Okay, I'm gonna save for angel.
Yeah.
Uh, let's look for some secrets.
This could be it right here.
Nope.
Not that one.
I'm kind of moving away from the center of the map though, so...
Maybe not.
I don't know.
I feel like that was the only real possibility here.
Actually, there is one more that's kind of centralized.
This one.
Hey, nice.
We get money!
Was there anything I needed in the shop?
Let's go have a look.
Sharp key.
Oh, oh!
This one!
Obviously!
We want more options!
I even said it!
Yes!
More options, please.
Let's go.
What's this bullshit?
Okay.
Oh, man.
Oh, no.
What the hell?
How did he poop when he wasn't even there?
You saw that?
It's like playing Snake here.
But Diagonal Snake.
And it's kind of different.
But it's not actually Snake.
It's something else.
It's like I'm playing Binding of Isaac.
I don't trust.
Holy shit!
Wow!
More money.
Oh, god.
Shit!
This room is insane!
You're
insanity, man!
Holy fuck!
The game was just like, Nope, you are not getting Angel today!
I can tell you that much.
Don't even think about it.
Fucking difficulty got ramped to 11 all of a sudden!
Jesus Christ!
That's good.
That's not good.
Okay,
let's go west.
I'm so triggered about my Angel situation here.
It's crap.
I was too fast anyway, right?
Let's not do boss yet.
I mean...
Okay, there is a...
12% chance that we get Angel.
There's a chance!
It could happen.
Oh, god!
That was a tough room as well.
This entire level has been insanely difficult.
Okay.
One thing I've noticed is that these guys that are colored, they have way more HP.
They have way more HP.
Jesus trying to cut me off there.
Insane.
In the membrane.
Staying in the brain!
Haven't heard Temples of Boom in a long time, actually.
Ohoyoyoy!
Very good.
Anything worth getting?
Uh...
Tarot Cloth doubles the effects of most cards.
Hmm.
That is actually kind of cool.
Why not?
The chariot.
So that...
Wait, so that means for 24 seconds?
I get to run around like a madman?
That's kind of crazy!
And I like it.
In fact, let me buy this as well.
Are you a wizard?
Hattie!
Get a wizard.
How long does this last?
Like 30 seconds or something.
It lasts a while, for sure.
This is very annoying.
Oh, it's over.
We're back to normal.
I feel like my attack speed is very low.
I need more tears.
Open your mouth.
What a weird floor.
I could do a curse room.
Nah, let's go boss.
It's boss time.
Let's hope for something good.
Let's hope for more HP, actually.
Or maybe another injection mechanism.
I would like that too.
Oh, this guy's tough.
The good news is we already lost Angel, so...
Maybe use this, actually.
Oh, yeah.
Actually, maybe it's just about timing.
I know approximately when he's gonna jump, right?
And
move...
Now.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And now.
Okay, he's doing that.
Yeah!
Look at me go.
For center.
Hey!
I'll take that.
That's pretty good.
We could maybe go step.
No, I need this half a blue heart for buffer reasons.
We could look for a secret, though, before we go.
I'm thinking right there.
That's sort of centralized, right?
No, never mind.
Maybe down here, then.
Uh, wait, what?
Wait, how was the bottom looking here?
Looking good, okay.
Left is looking...
Okay, yeah, that could actually work.
No!
Could be over there, then.
That's sort of centralized.
Shit.
Okay, I see it, I see it.
Right here.
Let me check the bottom part.
Okay, that's solid.
No!
What do you want from me?
Where is it?
I give up.
I feel like I'm operating on false assumptions here, anyway.
Like, on one side, I'm kind of pulling these theories out of my ass, but on the other side, or on the other hand, I feel like it's quite successful a lot of the time.
I'm not sure.
Okay, placenta is good, though.
73 alien.
I mean, angel.
Alien.
This room is gonna be tough.
I'm gonna wait.
What?
Shit.
Scary.
Fuck me.
Holy shit.
Well fucking done there, Charles.
Uh...
I'm feeling lucky.
Then again...
The penny is good early on.
I also have the chariots.
You know what?
I don't like this room.
I'm gonna have to do this.
I feel bad about this.
Sometimes you gotta do it, you know?
Play it safe.
Oh god.
I am poor.
No.
I have to do it.
I would have lost my buffer.
I know it for a fact.
Even though it would have been nice on the boss, right?
Wait, I can't go anywhere.
Okay.
Mystery Egg or Ouija Board.
I think I like Spectral Tears and Tears.
Yep.
Definitely.
Big fan of that.
Pills.
I'm definitely not stepping on those.
Not right now.
Shit.
I'm stuck here!
Okay, I'm fine.
Holy shit.
I'm playing my heart out right now.
Okay, this room is not too bad, I guess.
Oh wait, you have Spectral Tears!
Yeah!
Massive.
There's the boss.
I think we just go for it.
Brownie?
What the hell?
That's a new one!
Never seen this!
Is he gonna charge me?
Or what's happening here?
No wait, I've seen this guy before.
I think.
This is familiar looking.
What is this creepies doing?
Is that good for me?
Okay, he becomes a little common poop.
Dude, I nailed that without taking damage!
Wow!
Speed for me and Angel!
Okay!
That's not bad!
These amount of damage right there?
Um, I can even, uh, let me think.
Wait, what character am I playing?
Oh yeah, I wanted to go kill Isaac, so fuck these guys.
I still have a shop, but I don't have any money.
I think I'm just gonna move on.
Because I still have a buffer.
Okay, so this is the mom floor.
Even with all this damage, I feel like I'm lacking damage.
Oh no.
Oh, that's so big!
I needed that.
Don't get hit now, don't get hit now!
Solid.
Treasure room.
Um, Rotten Baby or Box of- I hate both of these, man.
I guess if I have to choose, I'm gonna get Rotten Baby.
What?!
Yo!
Okay.
I'm actually happy it's this guy this time, because I don't have any money anyway.
One of the few times I'm happy about not getting a shop.
Let's find the boss.
We have no more business here.
Oh my god.
I'm gonna jump on me.
Yeah.
No.
Hate that pill.
Nope.
I feel the damage increase against those guys for sure.
Oh no, this room is gonna be cancer.
Keep an eye on the shadows.
Shit!
Oh, whoa, whoa.
Show me that boss already.
Oh yeah, I have spectral tears.
But I don't have spectral shoes.
Wish I had.
Oh!
Nice!
More speed.
This is a fool card.
Do I want it?
No.
I'm going towards Isaac.
It's kind of impressive how I managed to pick every single path except the one that leads to the boss.
And there goes my buffer.
I'm fucked.
Yeah.
God damn it.
Like, how did I fucking exhaust every option except the boss route?
It's impressive, really.
Oi.
Good.
Dude, I fucking killed it.
Wow!
I'm getting good at dealing with mom.
Holy crap.
So I need to take the Polaroid this time around.
That's how that works.
Cause we gotta go up.
Stairway.
To heaven.
Let's do Fight Club.
Boom!
I did it cause it felt good, okay?
Don't question my motives.
Oh my god.
My buffer is gone.
I think we can say goodbye to the Angel Dream.
Especially with a room like this, I gotta use it.
Christ.
Wow.
Oh, we got a big guy.
Solid.
I think we can say goodbye to this Eternal Heart as well, if we're being honest.
Oh!
Damn it.
Wait, the Eternal Heart also protects against losing Angel.
Oh, fuck!
Well, there goes my chance.
Never mind.
Dream is dead.
It is so dead.
Ugh!
Oh my god, what the... Dude, are we just cooked?
Is it just over?
Oh!
Wait, four.
Four, four, four, four.
Oh, I don't know what it is!
Okay.
I'm doing it.
What happened?
I'm scared.
Placenta!
Yes!
Plamicenta!
I thought I had the upper hand with Spectral Tears, but they had Spectral Shoes.
Library!
Book of Shadows?
Satanic!
Absolutely!
Yeah!
Very nice.
One of the best items in the game.
Temperance.
Oh!
Spawns two blood donation machines.
Oh well.
You know what?
Maybe that's for the best.
With the Satanic Bible, honestly, I prefer it.
No cope.
This was good for me.
We also have a Bookworm now.
That's gonna help our damage.
Massive!
Oh god.
Oof.
Alright, boss time.
Satanic Bible came in clutch.
Wait, what was that?
Did you see that animation?
That was weird.
He did a jump animation, but then he decided to split instead.
Very odd.
That was beautiful.
So I can sacrifice a heart for this.
I... yeah.
Why not?
I do wonder if that will work on the little skeletal things that split into many small ones.
If each one of those little small skeleton things have a chance to, you know, and the power tools.
Uh, why is there no stairway to heaven?
Maybe it's not yet.
Oh yeah, it's probably here.
Show me what's inside of here.
Ah, okay.
Well, I guess it's actually okay since there's no more shops anyway.
I'm gonna be here a while.
I actually saved them from that explosion.
Wait, actually, wait.
Oh!
Okay, so if the little...
uh, horn effect is on the initial bone and it splits, it splits into many smaller.
But it can't turn into, like, a little horn on impact with a wall.
Oh my god, that's actually sick.
More bombs is good.
You know what?
Maybe I'll wait with this until I clear the entire map here, because maybe there's something else I can spend my money on.
I'm gonna end up in a situation where I'm like, damn, I shouldn't have spent all my money, you know?
And it's gonna feel bad.
What the fuck?
That was a crazy dodge from me right there.
Ah, shit.
When we go back, grab this.
Actually, yeah.
Blow up.
Wait, we have an eternal heart?
I don't know where we got that.
Oh, it's from the item that gives us one every floor.
Right.
Oh my god.
Insane.
I wouldn't mind a bit more luck.
Gonna come this way.
Okay.
Worms.
Man, I really like the little, uh, skeletal bones.
Good item.
Oh, I tried to dodge it!
Rough.
What are these enemies?
There's so many of them!
And I'm...
This is like the first time I've ever seen them as well, and there's so many.
Suddenly they're everywhere, look!
It's crazy.
I hear a boss.
Damn.
Here.
Yeah.
Here we go.
It lives!
Good.
Focus.
Fuck.
Nice.
Nice!
We even get a demon.
Since we have an eternal heart, I think it's okay.
We can take a demon.
Wait, what is that little thing?
Bloody lust grants a stack and damage bonus?
No.
Yes.
Absolutely yes.
What?
Oh, shit.
Oh my god, this bible better fucking take us to the promised land now.
Here we go!
It's Isaac time!
Massive, massive, massive.
Yep!
I thought I just blew up my blue heart.
But that's not how that works.
Wait, am I flying?
No, I'm not.
Skeleton versus skeleton!
Yeah, how you like that, huh?
That's how it feels when you throw bones at people.
It doesn't feel good.
Oi, oi, oi.
I also have spectral tears.
I like them apples.
Oh, look at this room.
I need more tears.
Oh god.
Oh!
Holy crap.
Money.
I kind of want to find more good cards.
Because I want to see what their double effect is, you know?
Like how good it is.
I want to feel it.
So this is, this is it.
I think we just go in there and murder him.
Could also keep exploring a little bit.
Nah.
Let's do it.
I think it's my specialty.
I'm so good at this guy.
I don't know how I just got hit.
Oh god.
He's different.
He's different than normal.
He's not like this usually.
He has ads and shit now.
That's not normal.
Come on.
No problem.
Here we go.
Wait, what?
Oh, right.
There's more.
The guillotine.
Okay, so this is the one with the freaking key here.
Got it.
Whoa!
Wait a sec.
I think this is worth.
What is that?
Hourglass.
Cursed Eye is shit.
I'm taking this.
Everything jar.
Anything is possible?
Spawns the item displayed in the jars icon.
Can be activated with any number of charges.
The displayed reward improves with more charges.
Activating with a full 12 charges results in a completely random effect.
Wow!
I mean, that's exciting, but I mean, I gotta go with the Bible.
Then again, glowing hourglass.
So we use the Bible for clearing, and then when it's boss time, we do this.
That's the plan.
It's a good plan.
Man, we're shooting fast now.
But the damage is very low.
I don't know if this is worth it.
I can't really tell.
No, it's definitely worth, right?
It feels good.
Oh my fucking god.
This room was insane.
There's boats everywhere.
Fast bombs has appeared.
I don't know what I did to unlock that.
But okay.
More unlocks is good.
Holy shit.
Pay to win?
No.
Too late for that.
Like a weird acceleration on those small ones.
When they move.
Dude, getting these blue hearts is actually massive.
Oh my god!
Damn, what a room.
Uh...
I think I keep clearing.
Yes.
We're getting filled up with hearts here.
No!
But the good news is, we have wafer.
That really is gonna make a big difference.
Shit, man.
Hey!
I like it.
Come lard.
Oh lordy.
I'm definitely not doing as much damage as I did before, I'm pretty sure.
But it's pretty good at AoE, you know?
Because they go everywhere, these little bones.
That's a nice room.
Wait, I can't damage that guy?
I didn't get to charge that much, huh?
Super Ball.
10% chance to fire a Bouncing Tear.
Um...
Yeah, actually.
That's nice.
Let's go to the boss night, we have full health.
This is the moment.
And we're also gonna pick up one of those items on the way.
I'm gonna use glowing hourglass.
That should do it.
Ah!
Thank god we have the wafer.
Okay, focus up, focus.
What was that sound just now?
Oh, is he doing something?
The hell is happening?
Yeah, yeah.
No problem.
I should jump down.
We're going further.
Oh no.
This is Tarantino's favorite boss.
Wait, I can't even see my HP.
Damn.
My damage is low.
Like, it took me forever to kill that guy, you know?
Oh wait, I forgot my Bible!
Man.
We gotta find the boss fast.
That's all I'm saying.
How is that?
Oh wait, we're not done here.
Uh, no.
No thanks.
Please let me find the boss fast.
For once.
I beg you.
Prevents greed from appearing?
Is that the guy?
The boss and the...
I guess it is.
Well, there is no room here, of course.
Oh no.
There's a mushroom!
Very nice.
That's sick.
I'm gonna do a bit of gambling here.
I mean, what else am I gonna spend my money on?
Wait, there's a chance we get money equals power somehow, right?
So let's just...
Yeah, let's wait.
Chance is very low, but it's there.
It's an awkward room for mom.
What the hell?
Whoa!
Man, rip the bit rate on the VOD on YouTube.
I'm sorry guys.
Or even on Twitch.
This build right here is a bit rate killer.
They're invisible!
Just shoot at anything and hope something lands.
Hey, it's really nice of clearing poop.
Oh my god.
Destroy him!
Why won't they die?
There we go.
Finally.
Speed down?
No thanks.
I don't know how much HP I have.
I must have a lot still.
Skeleton versus skeleton.
Let's see how much you like this.
You like that, huh?
Bastard.
What the hell?
Why is he healing?
Oh, because the other guy was alive?
I'm confused.
Okay, there's two bosses here.
Loki.
Not the inanimate objects.
As long as I stay in the center, they're not gonna shoot.
Stay in the center.
Wait, am I destroying the statues with my hand?
Yeah, I am!
Look at that!
That's awesome!
Amazing.
Oh, killer rift!
That's a great one.
Fantastic.
The frail.
There's gonna be black holes at...
Oh my god, what the...
This is chaos.
No, he hit me.
Pyromaniac!
I wish I could see my HP.
Okay, I have full HP.
Now I just need Ipecac or something.
I think that was Placenta just now.
I need to be able to fly soon.
Like, flying is the only thing I really need here.
The Empress.
Oh, that's a big one for me, guys!
4.5 damage with this attack speed is incredible.
We're gonna save this for the ultimate boss here.
It is going to slap, I'm telling you.
Okay.
Let's do it.
Dude, the black holes are gonna just suck in all these projectiles.
Look at that!
He can't do anything!
Stay mad, bro!
Let me get to the other side.
This is great!
Hey, how you doing, son?
Curse of the Tower.
I don't like it.
Actually, I love this!
I love this!
Me likey!
Mucho, mucho, macho.
Nachos.
Guadalupe.
Blow me up!
I love explosions now.
In fact, why would I just run into enemies?
I have Wafer.
I take half a damage.
I get massively healed.
This is like an insane strategy.
You can't handle my black holes.
You cannot handle it.
Okay, where do we go next?
Let's go up here.
Kill me!
Oh wait, I'm probably fully healed.
I don't know how many red hearts I have.
It's not that many, I think.
I mostly had black hearts and blue hearts.
The Forsaken.
Wow, he gonna die fast.
Jesus.
The black bean.
Upon taking damage, Isaac releases several farts.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I mean, I'm gonna be unstoppable when I take damage.
Uh-oh.
Yeah, I like explosions.
Don't be afraid of it.
Embrace it.
Let's go here.
I love it.
I can't wait to see my HP, man.
Trick with a black heart.
Nah.
Actually, yeah.
Why not?
Mama Gertie!
Whoa!
Let's do Are You a Wizard?
Yeah!
Bombs galore!
We love the bombs!
Holy shit!
Mama Gertie had no chance.
Wait, this is like a mini version of the guy from the Beast's boss fight.
Geesh!
Geesh your laptop!
I will never stop referencing Lemmy, okay?
Yeah, actually, that's good for me.
Red HP is good for me now.
Monstro.
What the fuck is happening?
I'm taking a lot of damage.
I could revert, but I'm not gonna.
I'll keep this hourglass.
I need to find just a bit more damage up, and then I'm happy.
Dude, where's the last boss?
What the?
What the fuck is happening?
Huh?
There we go!
My black holes are too strong for you, Traveler.
My damage is not great here.
It's really not.
But I mean, I'm getting it done.
Morphing into all the bosses.
Holy crap.
Oh, he mad now.
The tower just had an effect there.
Is that Mom?
Dude, this is insane.
I never thought I would see myself playing a game like this with this much shit on the screen.
Like, this is like the most bullet hell-ish bullet hell I've ever bullet hell.
I don't know how much HP I have.
It's really, really discombobulating, not knowing that.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
This is good damage.
What the fuck?
He was bugging.
Oh.
Oh, shit.
I don't know how much HP I have.
I try to bomb myself routinely, just to see if I can heal.
I think we did it.
Wonderful.
Absolutely wonderful.
Shade has appeared.
Dude, we are on a fucking roll right now.
Win streak of four.
That's a record for me.
I gotta end it on that.
I'm not gonna ruin it.
No way.
Fuck yeah.
Amazing.
Absolutely amazing.
What up, guys?
What did you think of that one, huh?
Man, from start to finish.
Banger, banger, banger.
Was there a lot of doubters today?
How many doubters were in the chat?
You doubted and ended up wanting you to win so bad.
Oh, okay.
I like it.
I guess it's a win-win then.
If you want me to win and you gamble on doubting or on me losing, then you get happy no matter what happens.
What's my take on aliens?
They're out there, man.
I want to believe.
I mean, we are out here.
Why shouldn't someone else be?
It was so alien today, you're right.
Yeah, first time we got guppy.
We actually unlocked something by doing that.
We unlocked challenge eight.
So maybe next time challenges, just because we can keep the four-win streak going, you know?
That number's gonna stay there and look nice when we do the challenges.
I would love for the alien to come out, G-Game.
Makes me want to watch E.T.
I haven't seen that since I was a kid.
I did watch the latest Spielberg movie and I was like, what the fuck is this crap, dude?
What is Spielberg doing?
Does he have dementia or something?
Like, what is wrong with him?
That is a terrible movie.
Yeah, he's totally washed.
His glory days are over, man.
Yeah, this disclosure day was so bad.
The latest one he made.
And I usually love Spielberg, you know?
I actually did like The Fablements, which is a recent one he did.
Like, he still has some chops, but it feels like his heart wasn't in this one, you know?
The Fablements was pretty good.
God, I feel good after that.
That is like the best feeling ever, you know?
Winning in video games.
Is there a better feeling on earth?
It's better than sex.
You heard it here.
I think it's because it's an old script.
Nah, but also just the directing of it was horrible.
I didn't like pretty much any of it.
Yeah, next time is Sims, definitely.
Aliens will not be Silicon.
Wait, what?
What does that mean?
But imagine that coming out in 2008.
It's still gonna be bad.
That has nothing to do with the age.
Or the year.
If this came out in 1998, I would still say it's a bad movie.
It would probably be nice to look at in the movies, because, you know...
It's kind of pretty.
Honestly, it's not even that pretty.
In 1998, man, we had The Matrix.
Are you kidding me?
The Matrix has aged like fine wine.
I do do this full-time, Svarios.
But even yesterday, I was considering maybe finding like a small part-time job.
Just because I realized that, yes, I'm doing this full-time, but I'm not actually doing it full-time.
You know, in Denmark, the work week is like 37 and a half hours.
I'm not working that in a week.
You know?
I have time left over where I don't know what to do with myself.
And you could say, just play more games.
But I can't.
I mean, I can, but I'm not going to enjoy it.
I just can't play that many games, you know?
I get saturated if I play too much of it.
And then the whole magical feeling of it goes away.
So I have to moderate it.
Unlimited games, but no games.
Exactly.
Kinda.
Which movie would you say has the best aliens?
Easiest answer of my life.
Contact.
Less is more.
I don't want to spoil anything, but Contact is a fucking masterpiece.
It's my second favorite movie of all time.
And it used to be my favorite movie until Black Swan came out.
There's just nothing like windsurfing with your dad.
In Pensacola.
No, that's not about...
No, you're thinking of, uh...
The Arrival.
RC Big.
That's also a good movie.
I like that one too.
Great feeling.
Just nice visuals and...
Cool story.
Bro.
By the way, one of my all-time favorite sci-fi movies...
That is severely underrated.
Is Sphere.
I would say it's better than the book.
By...
I'm gonna butcher his name.
Michael...
Crichton?
I don't know.
How do I say it?
You know who I mean?
How do I pronounce that?
Yeah, Semicus made it.
It's so good.
I fucking love Contact.
It may even be my favorite movie.
I don't know.
I haven't seen it in a while.
But I've definitely seen that movie.
Like, eight times or something.
It used to be my test...
Of whether or not I wanted to be with a girl I found, you know?
Like, I would date her for a while.
And then the big moment came, you know?
I invite her home.
I make her nice food.
And she's like, oh my god.
She's gonna try to sex me.
But then I'm like...
I put on the fucking Contact movie on DVD.
And see how she reacts.
If she doesn't...
If she hates that movie, then she's out.
That's...
That's the test.
You know?
I've not watched or read The Three-Body Problem.
But I heard it's good.
Crichton.
Same lame...
Same...
I thought you said same lame last name as me.
Okay, I see.
Crichton.
So I said it right the first time.
Michael Crichton.
Or Michael Crichton.
Yeah.
Have you read any Carl Sagan?
I have!
I have read...
I actually have it on my bookshelf here.
The one is called...
I actually didn't like...
Fuck, what is the name of it?
The one he made a TV show out of.
The actual book, I didn't like that very much.
But I loved...
I loved Science as a Candle in the Dark.
And also, Contact, the book...
I don't think it's that good.
The movie is so much better.
Yeah, Cosmos, that one.
The book was alright for that one.
But I preferred the TV show.
Because it's the first one I watched and I was a kid and I was fucking enamored with it, you know?
I mean, it's still a good book, Contact.
But the movie is just so much better.
It's one of the rare instances where the movie is...
Like, outshines the book completely.
But it's also because I really love Jodie Foster and she kills it in that one.
Yeah, the TV show is amazing.
It's what got me into science, man.
When I started high school, I was actually on...
On the linguistics path.
We had, like, certain paths you could go on, you know?
If you were a math guy, you would do the sciences.
Or you could do the arts and all that stuff, right?
Yeah, Demon Haunted World, that one.
I used to be on the, you know, the writing and the language thing.
Because I was so bad at math.
I hated it.
I hated physics.
I hated math.
I hated everything.
But then I watched Cosmos with Carl Sagan.
That and the combination of having the best science teacher of all time.
Or I should say, physics teacher and math teacher just made me switch completely.
One year into my studies there, in high school, I started over.
And at the time, I didn't even know what a coordinate system was.
And by the end of those three years, I was writing my, not thesis, but the equivalent in high school on the special relativity from Einstein, you know?
That's the progress I made in three years.
I got consumed by it.
It changed my life.
Yeah, a good teacher is...
Like, being a teacher is one of the most noble jobs in the world, honestly.
It really is.
You have such a big responsibility for shaping the future of so many children.
It's crazy.
And I had my fair share of terrible teachers, you know?
Made me hate their subject.
It's their responsibility.
When is the new Red Dead 2 episode coming out?
It's not gonna be for a while.
I have technical issues with it.
Although, I'm actually slowly starting to back up my computer for my yearly, or I should say, annual...
bi-annual reinstall of Windows.
I was thinking, maybe I'll just quickly try and install Linux, since I'm doing this anyway.
Try to run the game and see if it's something to do with that.
And then switch back to Windows just to test, you know?
It would be a good opportunity to do it.
So excited to see the end of Baldur's Gate 3.
Are you ready?
I actually played, like, four to five hours of it, and I...
It's still on my YouTube.
But I never continued, because I actually had a lot of stuff going on at the time.
And I knew this game would consume my life.
And it was very irresponsible to keep playing it.
And now I really never got back into it.
And then I thought, ah, I wanna play the first Baldur's Gate first.
Before I played the third, you know?
Because I wanted some more backstory and lore and all that.
But...
One day for sure.
Baldur's Gate 3 will happen again one day.
But I'm gonna start over.
I'm not gonna continue my save.
I'm not even sure my save still exists.
It probably does, because Steam saves, you know?
Or Steam Cloud, but...
What books did I use when studying Astro?
Oh my god.
Let me see.
I can just look at it on my shelf.
I have Galaxies in the Universe by...
Spark and Gallagher.
Active Galactic Nuclei by Bradley M.
Peterson.
Let me see.
What else do I have?
Handbook of CCD Astronomy.
What else?
There's definitely more.
Stars in the Universe.
Theory of Stellar Structure and Evolution by...
Pryalnik.
I got a first name.
There's also other books, but yeah.
Basically, these are the books that...
The professors, you know, suggested that we get.
No, I didn't even leave the tutorial, Frank.
At least I don't think so.
It's been a while.
I almost don't remember anything.
I don't even remember the start of the game.
Isn't that crazy?
Like, it completely left my mind.
Are we gonna vote on a game after Isaac or XCOM finishes?
Maybe.
Maybe, maybe not.
I don't know.
I already have a mod in Isaac.
It's the...
Gym mod.
And that's about as far as I'm gonna take it.
At least for now.
Superland is actually on the backlog, I think.
By the way, the backlog is not entirely complete, you know?
I may miss some games here and there.
So if you notice that I'm missing something, or if there's a game I have played that is not on there, let me know, you know?
I'll fix it.
It's not perfect yet.
There's a mod that turns Jacob and Esau into Beavis and Butt-Head.
Really?
Are they...
Did they include the sounds as well of them laughing?
That would be epic.
I remember there was a lot of, uh...
Uh, what's the word?
Spelunky was all the rage.
Back when that came out.
There was a lot of people talking about it.
This is many, many years ago.
But I never got onto that wagon and joined everyone.
But I know it's very loved.
And it's also on my backlog.
Lisa the Painful has been recommended multiple times.
I have never heard of it.
But I'm gonna add it.
Lisa the Painful.
I mean, there's just so many games in my backlog already.
Let me see.
Lisa the Painful.
2014.
I guess Definitive Edition.
2023.
Ah!
Jackie!
Jesus!
Ah!
No.
Don't do that.
Okay.
It's added to the backlog.
I noticed you don't have Fez and Spelunky there.
I'll add those two.
I've heard that Fez has good music.
That's all I know about that game.
Uh, Spelunky.
There's a Spelunky 2 as well.
I'll just add the first.
It's implied that, you know.
Jackie, you wanna come up here?
Maybe you can hear her.
I don't know if you can hear her right now.
Hey, Jackie.
What do you want, huh?
You want food?
That's not yet.
We gotta stick to the schedule.
She's making, um...
What's the word?
With her paws right now on my tummy.
Biscuits.
Jackie.
She's making bread, yes.
Yeah, she can sense the end of the stream.
Every time I turn off the stream and I stop, uh, saying something for, like, 20 seconds, she always comes into my room, like, meow, meow, meow.
And then as soon as I stand up, she runs into the other room and jumps up on the couch and looks at me.
And is, like, ready to play.
You know?
It's become, like, a routine now.
At some point, I'm gonna have a camera ready to record the end of the stream when I say, okay, that's it, guys.
I'll see you later, you know?
Like, I'm out of here.
And then, uh, as soon as I take off my headphones, you'll see her run inside.
And I don't know how she knows, because she's sleeping a lot of the time.
I guess...
She's, like, in the back of her mind, she's just paying attention.
And she knows.
Oh, Jackie.
She's pushing the microphone with her paws.
What are you doing, Jackie?
Okay, you want it down?
Okay.
Off you go.
Holy shit!
A lot...
You need to...
I need to brush you.
You have so many loose hair.
Wow.
Okay.
Guys, I'm gonna leave.
And I'll see you in the next stream.
It's gonna be Sims next time.
Yeah.
Have a good one.
Bye-bye.